{
	"data": [
    {
      "question": "I did not know ___ he had arrived or not.",
      "a": "why",
      "b": "whether",
      "c": "when",
      "d": "how",
      "answer": "2",
      "explain": "- Whether...or not: used to say that something definitely will or will not happen whatever the situation is",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "40",
      "subcategorylv2": "6",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "Some people want to go hunting,___ others want to go fishing.",
      "a": "or",
      "b": "because",
      "c": "while",
      "d": "since",
      "answer": "3",
      "explain": "\n- While: used to emphasize the difference between two situations, activities",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "40",
      "subcategorylv2": "6",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "She had no sooner heard the news ___ she turned pale.",
      "a": "when",
      "b": "that",
      "c": "as",
      "d": "than",
      "answer": "4",
      "explain": "- No sooner...than: used to say that one thing happens immediately after another thing",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "40",
      "subcategorylv2": "6",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "Bad habits, ___ formed, are difficult to give up.",
      "a": "and",
      "b": "once",
      "c": "or",
      "d": "but",
      "answer": "2",
      "explain": "- Once: from the time when something happens",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "40",
      "subcategorylv2": "6",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "Everett did not get the letter in time ___.",
      "a": "since it was delivered late",
      "b": "since it was late delivered",
      "c": "because of it was delivered late",
      "d": "because it was late delivered",
      "answer": "1",
      "explain": "- Since: used to give the reason for something",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "40",
      "subcategorylv2": "6",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "It was not until the night was far advanced ___ the crowd dispersed.",
      "a": "when",
      "b": "before",
      "c": "that",
      "d": "though",
      "answer": "3",
      "explain": "- That: used to introduce a clause that refers to a fact, when describing it",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "40",
      "subcategorylv2": "6",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "The reason Virginia did not attend the concert is ___ the violinist was unpopular with the young.",
      "a": "because",
      "b": "since",
      "c": "what",
      "d": "that",
      "answer": "4",
      "explain": "\n- That: used to introduce a clause that refers to a fact, when describing it",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "40",
      "subcategorylv2": "6",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "We kept quiet ___ we would disturb the patients.",
      "a": "for fear",
      "b": "so as to",
      "c": "that",
      "d": "so that",
      "answer": "1",
      "explain": "\n- For: used to introduce the reason for something [= because] ",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "40",
      "subcategorylv2": "6",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "He is ahead of me not in English,___ in German.",
      "a": "when",
      "b": "but",
      "c": "so",
      "d": "or",
      "answer": "2",
      "explain": "- But: used to connect two statements or phrases when the second one adds something different or seems surprising after the first one",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "40",
      "subcategorylv2": "6",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "___ are fed into a tape recorder, they magnetize the particles on the tape in varying patterns.",
      "a": "Electric waves",
      "b": "Electric waves that",
      "c": "Because of electric waves",
      "d": "When electric waves",
      "answer": "4",
      "explain": "\n- When: used to mention a type of event or situation when talking about what happens on occasions of that type",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "40",
      "subcategorylv2": "6",
      "type": "1"
    }
  ]
}